ILGWU. Publications 5780 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Freedom Award Dinner: In Honor of David Dubinsky, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- The New York Times Magazine: Instead of the McCarthy Method, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- The Jewish Labor Movement in the United States, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Erkshter Yehrlikher Berkht Fun Der Dushoint Board ou Sanitory Kontrol Un Der Klouk, Sut un Skoyrt Industrie Fund Greyeter New York (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Special Report on Sanitary Conditions in the Shops of the Dress and Waist Industry (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Fourth Anniversary of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Jubilee Journal: Benjamin Kaplan 60th Birthday, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- 65th Birthday: Nicholas Kirtzman (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Know Your Price Settlements: Dressmakers' Union Handbook (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Know Your Union! (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Connaissez Votre Union (Box 13, Folder 2)
  French.
- Know Your Union-Third Edition, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Connaissez Votre Union- Troisieme Edition, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  French. 2 copies.
- Conoscete la Vostra Unione- Edizione Italiana, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Italian. 2 copies.
- Conoscete la Vostra Unione- Edizione Italiana, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Italian.
- Know Your Union- First Edition, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Know Your Union, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Joint Council Knitgoods Workers Union of the ILGWU and United Textile Workers of America: Know Your Union (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Know Your Union, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Labor Looks at Education, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Labor Looks at Education, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- The Reader's Digest Reprints, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Labor in the New Deal Decade, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- The Labor Movement and the NRA (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Labour Politics in the USA, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Labor Stuff, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Labor Unions and Spanish-Speaking Workers, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Labor's Opportunity Under the Industrial Recovery Act (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Labor's Stake in Public Goodwill, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- The Ladies' Garment Worker Vol.III, No.9, 1912 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Learning and Living the Union Way, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- The Left Wing in the Garment Unions, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Les Midinettes, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Let's Go! Manual for the Education Committees, ILGWU (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Louis Levy: Fifty Years of His Life, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Libertas Spring 1922 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Lo Que Todo Miembro Debe Saber Acerca De la Union (Box 14, Folder 3)
- The Lock-Out in the Cloak and Suit Industry, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- A Look Back: Pages out of American Labor's Past, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Looking Forward in the Popular Priced Dress Manufacturing Industry, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Report For Des Yohr 1917 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Yerlikher Barikht Fun Der Ekzerkoytiv Bord Fun Klouk Un Sut Opereytors Yunion Lokol 1, ILGWU (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Yerlikher Boricht Fun Der Ekzekutiv Board Fun Klouk Un Sut Opereytors Lokal 11 ILGWU (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Report and Financial Statement of the Executive Committee, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Report (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Report 1917-1918 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- 50th Anniversary: Cloak and Suit Operators' Union, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- 70th Anniversary of Local 10, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Souvenir Journal: Issues on the Occasion of the 50th Jubilee of the Cloak Operators' Union (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Fiftieth Anniversary of Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10, 1952 (Box 14.1, Folder 1)
- Local 10 Cutters' Almanac, 1962 (Box 14.1, Folder 2)
- Handbook for Members (Box 14.1, Folder 3)
- Handbook (Box 14.1, Folder 4)
- Second Souvenir Journal: Old Age and Relief Funds, 1936 (Box 14.1, Folder 5)
- Algemeyner Un Finanzieler Beriknt (Box 14.1, Folder 6)
- Local 10 Forges Ahead: Report to the Membership on Activities and Operations of Amalgamated Ladies Garment Cutters Union, ILGWU, 1941 (Box 14.1, Folder 7)
- Rifer-Makher Yunion Lokol Numer 17, ILGWU (Box 15, Folder 1)
- 30 Yoriker Yubileaus (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Fiftieth Anniversary Dinner/Banquet for Joseph Kessler, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- 25th Anniversary Jubilee of Local 21, ILGWU, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Dressmakers International Ball, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Preparing for a Career in Labor Leadership (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Report of the Delegation of Local 22 on the 23rd Biennial Convention of the ILGWU, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- We're Glad You're Here! (Box 15, Folder 8)
- …And This is Your Union! (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Report of the Ladies Waistmakers' Union, Local 25, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Hourly Table of Wages from $9 to $50 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- '33-'43: Ten Years of Progress (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Twentieth Anniversary, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Important Rules and Regulations: Relief Fund and Wage Schedule (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Y Esta Es Su Union, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Pressers 35 Jubilee, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- The Beltmakers: A History of Local 40 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Introducing Local 40 ILGWU (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Your Union and Your Union Dues (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Your Union Guide, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- 40th Anniversary Celebration of Dressmakers' Local 46, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Celebrating the Twenty-Fifth Anniversary, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Testimonial Dinner to Edward Molisani, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Local 48 Salutes ILGWU Golden Jubilee Convention, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Fourth Anniversary Celebration, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- The Pressers: Pioneers Forging Ahead (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Report of the Dress and Waist Pressers' Union, Local 60 to the Sixteenth Convention of ILGWU, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Report of the Dress and Waist Pressers Union, Local 60 to the 22nd Convention of the ILGWU, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- The Union Shipping Clerk: A Handy Reference Guide to Your Rights, Benefits and Responsibilities, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- 1909-1959 Fifty Years Local 62, ILGWU (Box 16, Folder 17)
- 40th Anniversary Local 64, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Twenty-Five Years of Local 66, ILGWU; Ten Years of Service, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Sew and Know: A Handy Guide to the Way Your Union Functions, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Local 89 ILGWU Jubilee, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- 25th Anniversary, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Qui Incomincia La Novella Storia (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Italian. 3 copies.
- They Speak for Themselves: To the Members of Our Union, To the Friends of Our Union (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Our Union, Our Convention (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Annual Report for the Year 1939 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Annual Report for 1940 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- We Do It Again, Annual Report for 1941 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- "Life, Liberty and the Pursuit of Happiness…" Annual Report for 1943 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- The Four Freedoms. Annual Report for 1944 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Annual Report of Local 91: 1946 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- This is Worth Fighting For! Annual Report for 1942 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Annual Report for Local 91: 1950 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- 50th Anniversary Local 91 ILGWU, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Forty Years, Local 91, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- 25th Anniversary Local 91 ILGWU, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- 25th Anniversary Silver Jubilee Celebration, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- 15th Anniversary Jubilee Book, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- 30th Anniversary Jubilee Celebration, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Local 99 Goes to War (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Local 99 Handbook (Box 18, Folder 8)
- "99" Letters tell the Story (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Meet Your Union (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Moving Forward Together: A 3-Year Progress Report (Box 18, Folder 11)
- 25th Years with the Dressmakers Union, Local 100, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Souvenir Journal: Second Anniversary Jubilee and Testimonial Dinner, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Your Job, Your Union and You (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Know Your Union, Questions and Answers (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Know Your Union (Box 19, Folder 1)
- The Goals We Share (Box 19, Folder 2)
- A Good Union Never Rests, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- A Good Union Never Rests (Box 19, Folder 4)
- A Good Union Never Rests- Second Edition (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Service Tells the Story, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Your Union Begins With You (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Local 108: A Report 1933-1953 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Iber 2 Yor Tetikayt Barikht Fun Der Ekzekutiv Board Fund Des Foeynigtn Klouk, Sut, Infants Un Tshidren Kout Opreytors Un Sempelmakher Yunion Lokal 117, ILGWU (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Algemeyne Tetigkaytn Lokal 117 Dzshulay 1939-Martsh 1942 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Algemeyne Tetigkaytn Lokal 117 Martsch 1942-Yanuar 1944 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- General Activities and Finance Reports, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  Yiddish and English. 2 copies.
- General Activities and Finance Reports, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- General Activities and Finance Reports, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Jubilee Journal: 75th Anniversary of the Cloak Operators' Union and 25 Years of the Merged Cloak Local 117, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  Yiddish and English. 5 copies.
- Information Bulletin, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Information Bulletin, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Information Bulletin: Get Acquainted with Your Union and the Benefits You Are Entitled To, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Reception and Banquet Honoring First Retirees. 25th Anniversary Celebration, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Local 132 ILGWU: 1937-1957 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- 16th Annual Dance, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- 20 Years of Progress: The Local 142 Story (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Your Union, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- 25th Anniversary, Local 185, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- 20 Years of Progress (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Ten Year Jubilee Banquet and Dance, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Union Des Ouvriers Du Vetement Pour Dames De Montreal: ILGWU Local 262, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  French and English. 2 copies.
- Honoring I. Melamed, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Manifesto Issued by the General Executive Board to the Cloakmakers and Dressmakers, 1928 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Der Manifest Fun Des Dushenergal Ekzekutiv Board En Di Kloukmakher Un Dresmakher (Box 20, Folder 4)
- A Manual for Trade Union Speakers (Box 20, Folder 5)
- A Manual for Trade Union Speakers, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- A Manual for Trade Union Speakers, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Mark-Downs in Women's Coat and Suit Industry: Their Cause and Control (Box 20, Folder 8)
- The McCarthy Balance Sheet (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Fifty Years of the ILGWU Union Health Center (Box 20, Folder 10)
  9 copies.
- Meet…The ILGWU, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Meet the ILGWU (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Meet Your Union (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Meet the Upper South Department, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Bulletin of the Merchants' Society of Ladies' Tailors and Dressmakers, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Bulletin of the Merchants' Society of Ladies' Tailors and Dressmakers, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- A Message from Workers to Workers (Box 20, Folder 17)
- The Story of Mary Brown, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  7 copies.
- The Midwest Department, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- The Midwest ILGWU Welcomes You! (Box 20, Folder 20)
- The Minneapolis Story (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Mooney and Billings Must Be Freed!, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- More Than Charity… (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Mother Goose Goes Union! (Box 20, Folder 24)
- "My Name Is Mary Brown" A Musical Narrative, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  8 copies.
- My Trip to Europe, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Needle Trades Left Wing Program, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Program Fun Linkn Fligl Fun Di Ngdl Treyds (Box 20, Folder 28)
- The Needle-Trades Union: A Labor Movement at Fifty (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Needles and Pins, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Booklets Issued to the 24th Convention of the ILGWU, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Bundle Control (Box 21, Folder 3)
- New York Cloak Joint Board: Booklet Issued to the 23rd Convention of the ILGWU, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Highlights of Four Years' Activity of the Joint Board Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Unions (Box 21, Folder 5)
- 37 Years Young! 1910-1947 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- The Record 1950-1953 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Report of the New York Cloak Joint Board to the Twenty Ninth Convention of the ILGWU, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Report of the New York Cloak Joint Board to the Thirtieth Convention of the ILGWU (Box 21, Folder 9)
- The New York Dress Industry Problems and Prospects, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Gerekhtigleyt (Box 21.1, Folder 1)
- Fiftieth Anniversary Cloakmakers Strike of 1910, 1960 (Box 21.1, Folder 2)
- 1910 Gerechtiekeit, 1960 (Box 21.1, Folder 3)
- Testimonial Dinner in Honor of Daniel Nisnavitz, 1951 (Box 21.1, Folder 4)
- Report 1950. ILGWU Jubilee Convention (Box 21.1, Folder 5)
- A Part of the ILGWU, 1959 (Box 21.1, Folder 6)
- Report to the Delegates: 31st Convention of the ILGWU, 1962 (Box 21.1, Folder 7)
- Official Opening of the ILGWU New Building and Health Center Souvenir, 1951 (Box 21.1, Folder 8)
- Operation ILGWU Education, 1956 (Box 21.1, Folder 9)
- New York: Our City, Our Union. 24th Convention of the ILGWU, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Our Educational Activities 1917-1934 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Our Union at Work: Summary Report of the Executive Board of Dressmakers Union, Local 22, ILGWU, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Our Union at Work: A Survey of the Activities of Dressmakers Union, Local 22, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Our Union: How it Works Labor Pamphlet #1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- The Outside System of Production in the Women's Garment Industry in the New York Market, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- A Basic Understanding of Patternmaking, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Picture of a Union…The ILGWU, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Piecework in the Silk-Dress Industry: Earnings, Hours and Production, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Louis Pine: Fifty Years Old, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Harold Rome's Musical Revue of the '30s: Pines and Needles (Box 23, Folder 3)
- How "Pins and Needles" Was Born (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Pins and Needles (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Pins and Needles (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Pins and Needles (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Pins and Needles flyers (Box 23, Folder 8)
- New Pins and Needles, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Pins and Needles, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Pins and Needles (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Labor Stage Inc.: Season of 1937-1938, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Plant Removal, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- United States Department of Labor Women's Bureau: A Policy Insuring Value to the Woman Buyer and a Livelihood to Apparel Makers, 1926 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- The Position of the ILGWU in Relation of CIO and AFL 1934-1938 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- The Principles of Unionism, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Program of Dressmakers Progressive Group, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Program Fun Di Dresmeykers Progresiv Grup Lokal 22 ILGWU (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Program of the Dressmakers Progressive Group, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Program Fun Der Dresmakher Progresiver Grupe Lokal 22, ILGWU (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Third Anniversary Dinner and Dance, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Progressive Unionism, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- The Prosanis Label (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Protocol of Peace, 1913 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Protocol of Peace in the Dress and Waist Industry (Box 23, Folder 21)
- The Ready-to-Wear Industry 1900-1950, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- The Record of Hitler's New Order in Europe (Box 24, Folder 1)
- The Reader's Digest, Vol. 48, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Retired and Remembered (Box 24, Folder 3)
- The Retirement Myth, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Revision of the Tariff on Women's Clothing, 1913 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Rift and Realignment in World Labor (Box 24, Folder 6)
- The Nation, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Rivera Murals, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Rivera Murals, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Review, Vol.4, No.1, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- The San Francisco General Strike and the Labor Movement, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Ratevet Di Yunion (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Security in the Later Years (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Seventh Avenue: A Searching New Appraisal of the Garment Industry, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- 75,000 Strong. Fraternal Greetings, 1933 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Etlikhe Verter Tru Di Kloukmakher Vegen Der Itstiger Lage (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Sew and Know, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Shall Strikes Be Outlawed?, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Shall Trade Unions Be Regulated By Law? (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Signature of 450,000, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  This publication is a presentation of the 65th Anniversary Convention of the ILGWU, Miami Beach, FL, May 1965. 4 copies.
- Report to the Golden Jubilee Convention ILGWU, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- The Story of the ILGWU, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- La Storia Della ILGWU, 1936 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- The Story of the ILGWU, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- The Story of the ILGWU: First Edition, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- The Story of the ILGWU Cooperatives (Box 25, Folder 7)
- The Story of Progress Among the Women's Garment Makers, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Structure and Functions of the Cloak Out-of-Town Department (Box 25.1, Folder 1)
- Structure and Functioning of the ILGWU, 1934 (Box 25.1, Folder 2)
- Structure and Functioning of the ILGWU (Box 25.1, Folder 3)
- Structure and Functioning of the ILGWU, 1947 (Box 25.1, Folder 4)
- Structure and Functioning of the ILGWU, 1958 (Box 25.1, Folder 5)
- Estrutura y Funcionamiento de la ILGWU, 1947 (Box 25.1, Folder 6)
- The Structure and Functioning of the ILGWU: An Outline, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- An Outline of the Structure and Government of the ILGWU, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- American Labor: The Magazine of Labor News, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- A Summary and Critique of the Law of Peaceful Picketing in New York, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- The Taft-Hartley Law: Its Effect on the Growth of the Labor Movement, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- '33-'43: Ten Years of Progress- The Story of the Blouse and Waistmakers' Union (Box 26, Folder 6)
- 25 Years of Progress: Silver Jubilee, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  Yiddish and English.
- Trade Unions and the War (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Training for Garment Jobs, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Training for Union Leadership (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Training for Union Service (Box 26, Folder 11)
- The Trouble with Operators, Local 1 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  Yiddish and English
- The Truth about Luigi Antonini (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of the Presidency of David Dubinksy, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  12 copies.
- Fiftieth Anniversary: First Union Health Center, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Union Interest in Engineering Techniques, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Official List: Union Shops in the Dress Industry, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- The Union Way: A Guide Toward Union Principles and Practice (Box 26, Folder 18)
- The United Cloakmaker, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Build the United Labor Party: The Communist Answer to Dubinsky, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Der Onkumender Vinter-Sezon (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Meet the Upper South Department: 26th Convention, ILGWU, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Directory of Offices and Services: Upper South Department, ILGWU (Box 26, Folder 23)
- The Upper South Department, ILGWU, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Tshalendush Fun Der Nodl Treyd Arbeter Indusrtieler Yunion (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Unity House-37 Years (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Workers Get Vacation in Poconos at Bargain, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Pennsylvania Register Vol.XXII, No.5, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Unity House- Forest Park, Pennsylvania (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Unity House Invites You This Summer, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- 12th Season Unity House, 1930 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Yours for a Happy Summer Vacation: Unity House (Box 26, Folder 25)
- A Resort in the Poconos Has the ILGWU Label, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Celebrating July 4th: Unity House (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Tariff 1972 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Tariff 1973 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Tariff 1974 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Worker's Unity House: Ninth Season, 1927 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Unity House (Box 26, Folder 25)
- A New Unity House, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Program May 25th to May 27th, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Unity House in the Poconos (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Breakfast Menu, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Dedication: Unity House Theatre (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Weekend at Unity House for Shop Chairmen and Chairladies Program, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Gateway to Fun and Frolic (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Unity House (Box 26, Folder 25)
- The Start of a Perfect Day Breakfast Menu (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Festivities: Unity House Decoration Day (Box 26, Folder 25)
- 70th Anniversary Local 10, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Teach Them to Drive (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Tariff 1975 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Unity House (Box 26, Folder 25)
- The Answer to Your Family Vacation Problem (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Come the Revolution (Box 26, Folder 25)
- The Birth of Tourism in Pike (Box 26, Folder 25)
- The Man on the Flying Trapeze and Two Letters (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Wage Tables (Box 27, Folder 2)
- 1941 Wages for 1941 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Wage Calculation Book (Box 27, Folder 4)
  Yiddish and English. 4 copies.
- Bulletin for Organizers and Active Members on the New Wage-Hour Law, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- What Every Member Should Know (Box 27, Folder 6)
- What Every Member Should Know About His Rights, Privileges and Duties (Box 27, Folder 7)
- What Every Member Should Know About His Rights, Privileges and Duties (Box 27, Folder 8)
- What Every Member Should Know About His Benefits, Rights and Duties in the Union (Box 27, Folder 9)
- What Every Member Should Know About His Benefits, Rights and Duties in the Union, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Census of Manufacturers: 1925. Wearing Apparel., 1927 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- What Will Tomorrow Bring to Dress and Sportswear Workers? (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Where Do We Stand in the World Today? (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Why Education is a Must in the ILGWU (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Why This Strike (Box 27, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Winnipeg: 15 Years of Progress, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- With These Hands Play (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Economic Cooperation Administration Office of the US Special Representative in Europe, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- "With These Hands" Synopsis (Box 27, Folder 17)
- With These Hands Advertisement Booklet (Box 27, Folder 17)
- With These Hands: A Preview to the Golden Jubilee Convention, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Workers' Education Pamphlet Series No.8- The Woman's Auxiliary to Trade Union and Workers' Education, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Women's Coat and Suit Industry (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Women's Coat and Suit Industry 1948 Supplement (Box 27, Folder 20)
- The Women's Garment Industry, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Womens' and Misses' Coat, Suit and Dress Study, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- The Womenswear Industry, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- A Worker Looks at Economics, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- World Labor's New Weapon, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Silver Jubilee, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- You and Your Union Teacher's Text for Filmstrip (Box 28, Folder 2)
- You and Your Union, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Your Union Agreement (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Your Union Dues (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Your Union is the ILGWU: Twenty-Eighth Convention ILGWU, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Rules and By-Laws (Box 28, Folder 6)
- So…You Want to Think It Over! (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Carnegie Hall Diamond Jubilee Seventy-Fifth Season 1966-1967 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Training Future Officers, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Proceedings and Debates of the 86th Congress, Second Session. Vol.106, No.118, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Everybody Sings (Box 28, Folder 11)
- From Division to Unity: AFL and CIO, The Position of the ILGWU from the Report to the General Executive Board to the 29th Convention of the ILGWU, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- The ILGWU:Record of Progress, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 13)